We have decided to
convince Roswell Corporation
to invest in our university.
This angel is so handsome.
But before we begin,
party hats for everyone.
Stop this nonsense!
If you won't sign that,
my investments in your companies
will be forfeited.
What?
Yes!
I'm Ezekiel Roswell
and we are married.
Damn, Zeke!
It's like twice the
size of our house!
Welcome to your new home.
What is it that you
really want me to know?
That I'm a mafia boss.
Even if you were the
worst person in the world,
I love you, Zeke.
I am Alyana Heartily-Ferrer.
This is my wife,
Aemie Ferrer-Roswell.
Zeke?
Mommy!
Mommy, who did this to you?!
Roswell.
The Roswells are our enemies.
From now on,
we will form an alliance.
We will bring down the Roswells.
This.
Is.
War.
We are launching a
war against the Roswells.
We will take down Ezekiel
Roswell once and for all!
I'm such a great actress, right?
So, are you confused now?
Have you caught Dong's
occasional slowness too?
It was all just
acting, don't worry.
Can I be an actress now?
I even look like
that talented actress,
Rhen Escaño.
Right?
Come on, agree with me.
I'm even letting you in on the plan.
Zeke said only we
should know about this.
But I'll share it with you
so you won't get confused.
Zeke and I are really okay.
Look.
I believe you.
Is there a problem,
Ezekiel Roswell?
What?
None.
What "none?"
There is!
There is a problem, Zeke!
The—
Zeke is so slow!
Dong almost gave it away there.
Dong really is such
a handful, isn't he?
Actually, he really did cry.
But I didn't show it
because, "Mafia Boss,"
crying all the time?!
Anyway, at least
you can see now?
Dong and I are really okay.
I'm even okay with the Yaji now.
Turns out they aren't our enemies.
The only real enemies
are the Swanseas.
Their leader is Violet Swansea.
And apparently, she wants to
replace Mommy as the Queen of Yaji.
I didn't even know Mommy
was the Queen of Yaji.
Anyway, we need to
keep an eye on Violet.
So the plan is to pretend
that Dong and I aren't okay.
Aemie,
you should stay at
my mansion for now
while your mother recovers.
Good thing Daddy beat me
to it before I could even ask.
Do we have fortune-telling
blood in the family?
I hope he doesn't figure out that
this is part of our plan.
Welcome home.
It's beautiful, right?
Do you like your room?
It's okay.
I will let you settle down.
It's so beautiful!
It's beautiful!
It's so pink!
Unlike Zeke's house,
there's no color at all!
Hello, Dong!
My room is so
beautiful, it's all pink!
As expected.
Huh?
What, are you a fortune teller?
Go ahead!
Guess what I'm doing right now.
Ribbit.
Tss. Stupid
Ri-bit!
Ribbit!
Are you okay, dear?
Ribbit.
Ribbit!
I'm okay.
That's Violet alright.
And she's wearing violet too.
All purple.
If I ever buy a baby,
I'll name her Pink.
Or maybe...
Magenta!
Or...
Scarlet?
Oh, no, wait!
Cloud—
Cloud...
Aemie.
What you've been
through is very painful.
That's why I'm
here to support you
in any way that I can.
You can call me Auntie Violet.
Or even better,
Mommy Violet if you want it.
I prefer Auntie Violet.
It hurts.
It's okay.
I'm used to being rejected.
Huh?
I thought she was evil?
Then why is she crying?
I feel sorry for her now.
Acting is so hard!
Please don't be sad.
It's okay, dear?
I understand you.
I know that I can never
replace your mother.
But just in case,
she won't wake up anymore—
Get out of my room.
Dear, I'm sorry.
Get out!
Dong.
Why did you drop the call?
So annoying!
That Violet is such
an attention seeker.
She came into my
room and made a scene.
She's really annoying.
Don't mind her.
Sleep now.
You need a lot of rest.
This is just the
beginning of our plan.
Right.
Okay, sure.
Goodnight, Dong.
You too, okay? Go
to sleep too, okay?
I love you.
Aww, are you blushing?
That night, I thought she had died.
We had no choice but to run.
Your mother and I got separated,
and we sent her and
your Auntie Sylvia ahead.
We agreed
to meet at the end of a bridge.
But...
But after the battle,
I couldn't find her.
I waited there for so long.
I wonder where
Daddy read this story.
It's not what Zeke told me at all.
I waited for so long.
But the only one who came...
was Violet.
Then she told me that
the Roswells had killed
your mother,
Sylvia,
and Amesyl.
Ro—
Roswells?
This is so annoying.
I'm crying because
that Violet's story is all wrong.
First, Mommy is still alive,
and so is my cuz.
Fake news.
So annoying!
Violet's obviously onto something.
Do they think they can escape from us?
Alright, Jerson, I'll go ahead.
It's too dangerous for you to go alone.
I don't get why, Jerson.
Even if the Roswells see me,
They don't know
I'm part of Swansea.
What does she think of me?
A fucking dumbass?
Hurry up.
Why don't we just kill Arcadia?
Let's just follow
Violet's plan for now.
Wait.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Oh.
Zeke, they want to
kill Guardian Angel.
I'll deal with the other guy.
You distract Blood
so he won't notice me.
Ah, shit.
Miss Aemie.
Who are you visiting here?
You!
I mean, you.
You're Zeke's friend, aren't you?
Yes, we used to be.
But we don't talk anymore.
You should be thankful.
Because I really think Zeke
still considers him a friend.
Because if he didn't,
who knows what Zeke
would've done to Ken here.
No?
Ah, wait, hold on.
Wait a second, Miss Aemie.
Maybe you'd like to
have dinner with me?
I still have something to do.
Ah.
Sure.
I guess I distracted Ken properly, huh?
Mission accomplished!
Oh, you guys caught up.
You probably thought
we'd really break up, huh?
Zeke and I planned all of that.
We're even going to
have our marriage annulled.
So they'd really fall for it.
Can you help my daughter get their
annulment done faster?
I'll take care of it.
Thank you.
Cuz, where have you been?
Dear,
I've been waiting for you.
Where did you go?
Oh, just around here.
Miss Aemie,
please sign this.
Annulment?
Don't worry, dear.
I'll make the annulment
process quick.
Once I sign this,
I'll be Aemie Ferrer.
Zeke and I won't
be married anymore.
The new title of this show will be,
My Ex-husband Is a Mafia Boss.
Oh, there.
A few tears to make it convincing.
Hello, Dong?
How are Milka and the others?
The three idiots are fine.
I miss you, wife.
I miss you, too.
But we were just together a while ago.
You, ah.
Ms. Aemie,
you're still talking to Mr. Roswell?
And so?
I thought he already
filed for an annulment?
But,
it looks like you two
are still sweet together.
Don't ask, and don't you
dare spill this to anyone.
Unless you wanna die.
It's beautiful, right?
Don't you dare
spill this to anyone.
Please sign this.
Hey, open this!
Hey, open this door!
Open this!
One!
Is this a prank?
This isn't funny
Hey!
Neighbors!
Hello?
Please, open this.
Hey.
If you're wondering why I'm here,
it's because of Auntie Violet!
She forced me to go on vacation.
Supposedly!
And you know what?
She even took all my gadgets.
Because she said I needed to relax.
Because I deserved it.
Do I really deserve this?
Hello?
Open this!
I'll tell my mommy on you!
What's so relaxing about this?!
Huh?
Do I look relaxed?
I've been here for seven days!
And then,
I told Zeke
I was just going on vacation.
Hey!
Dong, help please!
Dong!
Bro,
you're already standing.
You're just weak.
Oh, what is it, little bro?
After everything
you've been through,
haven't you learned
your lesson yet?
What do you think of me, sis?
I'm used to having
chicks fighting over me.
Okay.
I still can't fucking
contact her.
We've been looking for Ms. Aemie
for seven days now, but nothing.
I heard they sent Aemie Girl
to one of our 50 mansions.
Mm.
That's a lot.
Go ahead, Lerwick,
start digging a grave.
Want me to dig you a grave too
so we can also be together til death?
That's enough.
Okay.
At least she's safe.
Maybe it's better that she's not here.
We have to move now.
They're going to attack us, tonight.
Tonight?
Are you serious, boss?
What's the plan?
I will prepare Boul's dextrose.
You're incharge with the catheter, Kaizer.
Fucker.
Will you shut your fucking mouth?
Just tell us what we can do to help.
I know we're not
part of the Roswell,
but...
we're here to help.
We'll follow your
orders, Mr. Roswell.
Alright.
Spade Clifford,
Lerwick,
prepare the bombs.
Consider it done, boss.
Lee, Arcadia,
make sure Aemie's dad and the
rest of her family won't get hurt.
Tristan Klein, Meisha,
prepare the guns and ammo.
Lamperouge, Cassandra Heather,
prepare the cars.
The faster, the better.
And also,
make sure all the
civilians in the hospital
are evacuated.
What about me, boss?
In your case,
you and Ms. Ferrer will be our eyes.
Monitor everything.
I'll get the truck ready.
We'll monitor
everything through there.
I'll set up your cameras, Boul.
Wow!
Ja-Va! Love team!
Hey, Caileigh, Fauzia,
keep an eye on your guys, okay?
Cut that!
You only have three
hours left to prepare.
Can I join too?
No.
Boss, let Shin join.
I'll take care of her.
I'll keep an eye on them too.
Alright then.
Let's kill them all.
I need to get out of here.
Because I need to see
Mommy's surprise for Daddy.
You know what, Mommy?
I already signed the annulment papers.
I know it was—
just a joke and all, but
it still hurts.
Mommy, please wake up.
Please.
Wake up, Mommy.
Mommy.
Mommy?!
Don't shout, Baby Ae.
Huh?
I need your help.
Lock the door.
Okay, okay.
Oh, Mommy!
You can move after all?
And you still made me do it.
Baby Ae, do you have a gun there?
Mommy.
Yes, Mommy.
Zeke gave it to me.
It's okay.
Can I borrow your gun?
Yes, mom.
Here.
Let's keep it a secret
that I'm awake, okay?
I'll surprise your daddy.
Do you think they'll believe me if
I tell them I went through...
the ceiling?
Gotcha!
You thought I couldn't
get out of here, huh?
Thanks, Kate,
for telling us about
Aemie and Zeke's plan.
I'm going to see Alyana
at the other hospital.
I'll take care of her
while Eiji is busy
here with the Roswells.
Just give this to Mr. Roswell.
Supporting documents to the
Annulment papers.
He needs to sign it.
Got it, ma'am.
Let's go.
Let's go to Vash Boulstridge's room.
Do your job well, Kate.
Do you know what happens to souls
when they leave the human body?
You'll soon find out.
Four of them died.
Fiona and Wallace.
We have 20 minutes.
Those fucking Roswells!
Find them!
Calm down, sir.
You're not—
Don't touch me!
And get the fuck out of my way!
Let's go, hurry!
Who's this bitch?
I need to be at the hospital
before Eiji gets there.
Oh my god, Mama.
It's so creepy.
I know Daughter.
Stay inside the car.
Ma?
Do you know what you're doing, Miss?
Yes.
Ma!
How about you, Violet?
Do you know what you're doing?
Mama!
Sabrina!
How does it feel seeing your daughter
being killed right in front of you?
Sabrina!
What?
Is my wife here?
Where is she?
Blood took her there.
She's about to be there.
Fuck!
Better leave guys.
Our time is running out.
Dong!
Wife.
Yay!
I'm really good!
Wife!
Let's go.
Kid!
Let's finish this!
I'm warning you,
put your guns down!
Who are you to
order us around, huh?
Daddy!
Tsk!
I'm so good!
I'm really good!
Let's go.
Hey!
Seven minutes left before the explosion!
Omg! You're all gonna die.
Leave now!
Hey, what are you doing?
We're all going to die here!
Damn wife!
Marry me again.
Are you really asking me?
While things are really
getting out of hand.
No, I'm not asking
you. I'm stating plans.
We can't exactly get
married here in the hospital!
Just fucking listen!
I just need your fucking yes.
Wear this fucking ring.
So I have one damn good reason,
Not to left myself get fucking killed.
Yes!
I love you!
I fucking love you more
than fucking most, wife.
Come on. Until here?
Fuck you, Lamperouge!
Damn!
More of them are coming!
What the hell?!
Can't we get to the happy ending already?!
Let's finish this!
After such a long procession,
it still ends at the church.
Hmph!
I'm prettier than you anyway!
Stop the wedding!
Where is my wife?
Calm down, Mr. Roswell!
Aemie might just be stuck in traffic.
Boss!
Ma'am Aemie's bridal car
is at the other wedding.
Damn it!
What?
Who are you?
I'm the bride!
- What's happening?
- Oh no.
You!
Who are you?!
I'm the bride!
And my husband is
the one at the altar!
Go ahead, Miss!
You can be my wife instead!
Oh no!
No way! My condolences, bro!
Condolences?
Did Zeke stand me up?
Where did you hide Zeke, huh?
Who's Zeke?!
What's your problem, lady?
You're disrupting our wedding!
Move!
Or I'll blow your head off!
Why are you late, Zeke?
But, Miss.
We can always switch grooms.
No way.
I'm more handsome than him.
Let's go!
You're late!
You took so long!
- Why are you late?
- We're getting married!
Oh, kiss.
You look perfect.
Ezekiel Roswell.
Do you take this woman
to be thy wedded wife...
to live together in the
holy bounds of matrimony,
to love her,
comfort her,
honor and keep her
in sickness and in health,
and forsaking all others,
keep thee only unto her,
so long as you both shall live?
I won't stand here if I don't.
So yeah,
I freaking do.
Aemie Ferrer.
Do you take this man,
To be thy wedded husband,
to live together in the
holy bounds of matrimony
to love him,
comfort him,
honor and keep him,
in sickness and in health
and forsaking all others,
keep thee only unto him so
long as you both shall live?
Him?
Who was Father referring to?
Is he trying to set me
up with someone else?
What, wait. Let me think about it.
Wife.
He's referring to me.
Ahh.
Of course, Father. Yes, definitely.
Okay. Now,
Repeat after me,
I.
state your name.
I,
Ezekiel Roswell,
take thee, Aemie Ferrer
to be my wedded wife.
Take thee, Aemie Ferrer to be
Now you, young lady.
Repeat after me.
I, say your name.
No, say your name.
I,
Aemie Ferrer,
Oh, Father, that's me, Aemie.
Ahh!
Well, Father, you
didn't explain it properly.
Okay.
Let's do it once again.
I, Aemie Ferrer.
Take thee, Ezekiel Roswell,
To be my wedded husband.
To have and to hold,
From this day forward
For better, for worse,
- For better, for worse,
For richer, for poorer.
- For richer, for poorer.
In sickness and in health,
- In sickness and in health,
To love and to cherish,
- To love and to cherish,
Till death do us part,
Till death do us part.
According to God's holy ordinance,
- According to God's holy ordinance,
And there too, I pledge thee my faith.
- And there too, I pledge thee my faith.
You may now say your
personal vows for each other.
The feeling hit me the moment I saw you.
Stupidly sitting on the
ground in the middle of the road.
Yeah, I fell in love the first
time we made eye contact.
It was so immediate and powerful.
Far deeper and inexplicably beyond
any calculation of time and place.
You know me very well.
And yet you still managed to love
me despite all the reasons not to.
In short, ugly!
Ouch!
Out.
Get out of here.
I have learned a lot from you.
A lifetime won't be enough for me to
show you how much you mean to me.
I'm so proud,
and a one lucky bastard
to have you as my bride.
And to hear you say I do.
This day,
this special day, will
forever be remembered, wife.
I love you.
Oh no!
I wasn't prepared.
What will I say?
Uhm.
Hi, Dong.
Have you watched
my new Dollie movies?
Oh no.
Why, does it have to be dramatic?
How do I do this?
Help me out, guys.
Uhm.
Ah! I know.
Should I also tell the
story of how we first met?
Like that?
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
When I first saw you,
you almost ran me over because...
you were driving so fast.
Then you honked your horn so loudly.
You almost ran me over.
It wasn't.
That was so far away, wife.
This is my speech, don't interrupt me.
Oh, Father, he's interrupting me.
I thought then,
I was already in heaven because...
I thought you were an angel.
Are you insane?
But,
you weren't.
Because it turns out you were a driver.
- And then you tried to rob me.
- What?
Wait, just wait!
Wait, now I messed up.
Ah, but.
You were actually the one
I was looking for back then.
You really were Ezekiel Roswell.
Then,
after that, so many things happened.
You wear this.
Really?
Are we really married?
When are we going on our honeymoon?
Hey!
Don't tell me you're going
to make me drink that.
I thought you wanted this, Zeke.
That's cat milk.
Yeah!
No matter how grumpy you are,
and no matter how pointless
the things you say every day,
I'm still willing to share
my Dollie stickers with you,
even the ones I haven't bought yet.
And also...
you can borrow my dollies—
You talk too much, woman.
Can we proceed to the kissing scene?
Not too fast.
Please bring the ring.
Mr. Roswell.
Mrs. Roswell.
Loverboy.
By the power vested in me,
I now pronounce
you husband and wife.
You may now kiss the bride.
Hey wait, wait, wait!
Just wait, just wait, just wait, wait.
Father, you're wrong.
it should've been...
Dong and Wife.
Kiss!
You're officially mine, Aemie Ferrer.
Now and freaking forever.
Passionate.
Oh, wait.
Where's my mom?
Where did she go?
Mommy?
It's picture taking time already!
Where is she?
Where's mom?
Do you really think
that I am gonna
let you win that easily?
Damn you both!
Do you really think I
let you live for nothing?
I let you live so you can see everything.
I let you live for you to
see how happy we are.
Eiji and I.
Aemie and Ezekiel.
Now that you've seen everything.
I have no reason to let you live.
Oh there, Mommy!
Mommy, let's take a picture.
Where were you?
Sorry, I took care of something.
Ah, okay.
Let's go, go beside daddy.